<package>
    <id>fi.flodin.tonemanager</id>
    <name>ToneManager</name>
    <version>0.6.1-288</version>
    <compatibility>
        <firmware>
            <miniOS>9.0</miniOS>
            <otherVersions>unsupported</otherVersions>
        </firmware>
    </compatibility>
    <dependencies>
        <package>Applist</package>
        <package>libswift4</package>
    </dependencies>
    <descriptionlist>
        <description>Install ringtones from Audiko, Zedge without iTunes! Can also install ringtones downloaded with Safari or other apps.</description>
        <description><![CDATA[
            To install ringtones from Audiko/Zedge: <br />
            Download/mark as favorite ringtone in Audiko/Zedge. <br />
            Open ToneManager. If "Auto install" is enabled in preferences the ringtone will install automatically. <br />
            If the ringtone name is red it is not installed. Install by tapping "..." on the ringtone you want to install and choose install.<br />
            To install all ringtones in ToneManager press "Install all"
        ]]>
        </description>
        <description>This is a beta version which includes remote logging turned on by default. It can be disabled in the settings in the app. Because of the early beta status, expect crashes or other bugs.</description>
        <description><![CDATA[
            Features:<br />
            - Installs ringtones from Audiko/Zedge<br />
            - Scans any app you want for ringtones (as long as they are in the application Documents directory)<br />
            - Includes a simple file picker to import ringtone from custom folder<br />
            - Associates with sound files so you can import to ToneManager from the "Open in" menu from almost any app that allows you to open the share dialog for a sound file.<br />
            - Converts wav, aif, caf, mp3, mp4, snd, au, sd2, aiff, aifc, aac, m4a files to ringtones (m4r) <br />
            - Shortens ringtones longer than 30 seconds to only include the first 30 seconds <br />
            - Preview ringtones by tapping the ringtone row and press the play button<br />
        ]]>
        </description>
    </descriptionlist>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot>
            <description>ToneManager main view</description>
            <image>IMG1.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <changelog>
        <change>Added automatic file conversion to m4r</change>
        <change>Ringtones longer than 30 seconds will now be shortened to the first 30 seconds of the sound file</change>
        <change>Added send email button in settings that includes current settings, imported ringtones and important device info</change>
    </changelog>
    <links>
        <link>
            <name>/r/jailbreak</name>
            <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak</url>
            <iconclass>fa fa-reddit</iconclass>
        </link>
    </links>
</package>
