<package>
	<id>fi.flodin.tonemanager</id>
	<name>ToneManager</name>
	<version>0.5.1</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>9.0</miniOS>
            <otherVersions>unsupported</otherVersions>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
		<package>Applist</package>
        <package>libswift4</package>
	</dependencies>
	<descriptionlist>
        <description>Install ringtones from Audiko, Zedge without iTunes! Can also install ringtones downloaded with Safari or other apps.</description>
		<description><![CDATA[
            To install ringtones from Audiko/Zedge:
            Download/mark as favorite ringtone in Audiko/Zedge.
            Open ToneManager. If "Auto install" is enabled in preferences the ringtone will install automatically.
            If the ringtone name is red it is not installed. Install by tapping "..." on the ringtone you want to install and choose install.
            To install all ringtones in ToneManager press "Install all"
		]]>
		</description>
        <description>
            Dont try to import ringtones longer than 30 seconds. App will give you a warning, but will allow you to install it if you really want to...
        </description>
        <description>This is a beta version which includes remote logging turned on by default. It can be disabled in the settings in the app.</description>
        <description><![CDATA[
            Features:
             - Installs ringtones from Audiko/Zedge
             - Scans any app you want for ringtones (as long as they are in the application Document directory)
             - Includes a simple file picker to import ringtone from custom folder
             - Associates with various sound files so you can import to ToneManager from the "Open in" menu from ANY app that allows you to open the share dialog
             - Converts non-m4r files to m4r (TODO)
             - Preview ringtones by tapping the ringtone row and press the play button
        ]]>
        </description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot>
			<description>ToneHelper preferences pane</description>
			<image>IMG1.png</image>
		</screenshot>		
		<screenshot>
			<description>ToneHelper preferences pane showing imported ringtones. Swipe left to delete.</description>
			<image>IMG2.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <description>Ringtone picker view in Preferences with HUD overlay from Tonehelper.</description>
            <image>IMG3.png</image>
        </screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
        <change>First public beta</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>/r/jailbreak</name>
			<url>https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak</url>
			<iconclass>fa fa-reddit</iconclass>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>
